godchecker.com 2017-11-22

# Godchecker privacy policy

We aim to be a responsible website and have concocted the following privacy statement which we hope will bring you enlightenment. 

## Cookies

Cookies are tiny text files which websites use to store data on your device, usually to remember your preferences or add functionality. You can easily disable the use of cookies if you prefer. However some functionality may be lost. Please consult your browser documentation to learn how to disable cookies. 

Our policy is to avoid cookie technology unless essential to site functionality. We have worked hard to minimize our cookie use and currently (August 2015) this site only uses one cookie for users within the European Union zone to note their consent to cookie use. This cookie is placed to help us conform to the EU cookie policy law. If you are not accessing the site from the EU, no cookies will be stored. We do not store any personally identifiable information at any time. 

Any advertisements on this site served by Google and affiliated companies may use cookies. These third party cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this and other sites that use affiliated Google services. Cookies may also be stored for statistical or analytics purposes. You can learn more about this cookie usage, including how to opt-out, by visiting this page: [How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). 

**You are in full control of your cookie preferences and can delete or disable cookies at any time. Please consult your browser documentation to learn how to do this on your device. By continuing to use this website, you acknowledge that you have read and accepted this cookie policy and consent to the use of cookies as specified above.**

## Server logs

Like all web servers, the servers running this website may record statistics uch as the time, date, IP address and pages visited. This data is used only to compile general site statistics (such as the number of people visiting per day). We do not collect any personally identifiable information from visitors. 

## Email policy

All emails we receive are assumed to be for the furtherance of our work and will thefore be regarded as potentially publishable on the site or elsewhere unless you tell us otherwise. By sending us email you agree to grant us a non-exclusive, non-transferable right to quote or publish it (or part thereof) on our site and/or derivative works in perpetuity. If you do not agree to this condition, please indicate so by including the words NOT FOR PUBLICATION or similar phrase at the beginning of your message. 

If you contact us, all personal information you provide (such as name or email address) will be treated confidentially. We promise to respect your privacy and never reveal your email address to any third party unless compelled to by the forces of Satan. We are protected against all known forms of virus, spyware, trojans, worms and splim by RAGNORAK SECURITY, a division of Loki Enterprises. 

We do have a mailing list which we sometimes use to let people know about updates and new stuff. You can [subscribe here](http://www.godchecker.com/oracle/index.php?subscribe). If you write to us, you can additionally opt-in to the mailing list at the same time. We absolutely will not bombard your inbox every time we blow our noses. We use Mailchimp to handle our mailing list, one of the net's most respected email providers, so you can rest assured, etc etc. You can opt out at any time and we'll forget you ever existed. 

## Child privacy policy

We are proud to say that this website is used by many schools and education establishments. Please note that this site is not aimed at persons under 13 years old. If a person under 13 years of age wishes to use the site or contact us, this should ideally be done via their school or a parent. However, be assured that we do not collect, use or sell anybody's personal information. Names and email addresses are kept only as long as it takes to action them and are then deleted. 

_Policy page last updated 16 August 2015_

The Gods told us to do it. Go to top
